<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes"?><!-- Generated by SSuite Office - PAD File Generator Export -->  <XML_DIZ_INFO><MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO><MASTER_PAD_VERSION>1.0</MASTER_PAD_VERSION><MASTER_PAD_EDITOR>PAD File Generator 1.0 http://www.ssuitesoft.com</MASTER_PAD_EDITOR><MASTER_PAD_INFO>PAD: Portable Application Description</MASTER_PAD_INFO></MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO><Company_Info><Company_Name>SSuite Office Software</Company_Name><Address_1>P.O. Box 386</Address_1><Address_2>MyburghPark</Address_2><City_Town>Langebaan</City_Town><State_Province>Western-Cape</State_Province><Zip_Postal_Code>7357</Zip_Postal_Code><Country>Republic of South-Africa</Country><Company_WebSite_URL>https://www.ssuiteoffice.com/</Company_WebSite_URL><Contact_Info><Author_First_Name>Henk</Author_First_Name><Author_Last_Name>van Loo</Author_Last_Name><Author_Email>ssuitetech@yahoo.com</Author_Email><Contact_First_Name>Henk</Contact_First_Name><Contact_Last_Name>van Loo</Contact_Last_Name><Contact_Email>ssuitetech@yahoo.com</Contact_Email></Contact_Info><Support_Info><Sales_Email>supportservices@ssuiteoffice.com</Sales_Email><Support_Email>supportservices@ssuiteoffice.com</Support_Email><General_Email>supportservices@ssuiteoffice.com</General_Email><Sales_Phone/><Support_Phone/><General_Phone/><Fax_Phone/></Support_Info></Company_Info><Program_Info><Program_Name>SSuite NetSurfer Prometheus</Program_Name><Program_Version>2.8.10.1</Program_Version><Program_Release_Month>12</Program_Release_Month><Program_Release_Day>09</Program_Release_Day><Program_Release_Year>2025</Program_Release_Year><Program_Cost_Dollars/><Program_Cost_Other_Code/><Program_Cost_Other/><Program_Type>Freeware</Program_Type><Program_Release_Status>Major Update</Program_Release_Status><Program_Install_Support>Install and Uninstall</Program_Install_Support><Program_OS_Support>Win7 x32,Win7 x64,Win8 x32,Win8 x64,Win10 x32,Win10 x64,Win11 x32,Win11 x64,Win12 x32,Win12 x64,Win Other</Program_OS_Support><Program_Language>English</Program_Language><Program_Change_Info>This release is a general maintenance update, incorporating user feedback and comprehensive refactoring of the core application codebase to enhance stability and performance.</Program_Change_Info><Program_Specific_Category/><Program_Category_Class>Internet::Browsers</Program_Category_Class><Program_System_Requirements>1024 x 768 Display Size with Windows 7 and Beyond...</Program_System_Requirements><File_Info><File_Size_Bytes>48783004</File_Size_Bytes><File_Size_K>47640</File_Size_K><File_Size_MB>46.52</File_Size_MB></File_Info><Expire_Info><Has_Expire_Info/><Expire_Count/><Expire_Based_On/><Expire_Other_Info/><Expire_Month/><Expire_Day/><Expire_Year/></Expire_Info></Program_Info><Program_Descriptions><English><Keywords>netsurfer,chromium,web,browser,extension,extensions,x64,64bit,internet,online,website,privacy,secure,software,portable,fast,quick,educational</Keywords><Char_Desc_45>Prometheus offers blazing speed and security!</Char_Desc_45><Char_Desc_80>This browser is setting a new standard for modernized web surfing excellence!</Char_Desc_80><Char_Desc_250>SSuite NetSurfer Prometheus is a cutting-edge browser designed to offer lightning-fast speed, top-tier security, and unparalleled innovation. It empowers you to explore the digital world freely, without BigTech watching!</Char_Desc_250><Char_Desc_450>SSuite NetSurfer Prometheus is a cutting-edge browser offering lightning-fast speed, top-tier security, and unmatched innovation. With a lightweight architecture, it ensures smooth performance, even on less powerful devices. There are No performance dips, No sluggishness, just pure uninterrupted browsing bliss. Featuring an ad blocker, it provides a safe, streamlined browsing experience, free from BigTech control and typical Chromium limitations.</Char_Desc_450><Char_Desc_2000>SSuite NetSurfer Prometheus is a revolutionary browser that, rather than stealing fire, gifts you the blazing speed, security, and innovation needed to dominate the online digital realm without facing the wrath of BigTech, or any of the limitations of typical Chromium-based clones.

With its original design and forward-thinking functionality, NetSurfer Prometheus seeks not only to serve the individual but is also crafted to meet the needs of businesses seeking a reliable, secure browsing solution.

But here's the real kicker; NetSurfer Prometheus doesn't just copy what's already out there and then slap a "New and Improved" label on it. Oh no, it's got original flair...

From its extensive array of 35 selectable colored themes(from light and dark and everything in between, because you deserve choices, not ultimatums) to its user-friendly interface, this browser makes you feel like a digital trailblazer every time you open it. Whether you're a casual user or a business looking to upgrade your online game, this browser doesn't just let you surf the web; it makes you enjoy it.

When you launch SSuite NetSurfer Prometheus or open a new tab, the browser will immediately direct you to your preferred default homepage, which can be selected from a range of top-tier websites in the settings menu. This stands in contrast to other browsers that always default to a fixed branded homepage, cluttered with paid advertisements and sponsored links, which cannot be modified or removed.

There are No performance dips, No sluggishness; just pure, uninterrupted browsing bliss ensuring rapid page loads and smooth navigation across the web! Its lightweight design ensures smooth operation, even on less powerful devices, making it ideal for both intense gaming sessions and relaxed entertainment breaks.

So... take a seat, open a new tab, and get ready to browse the web like a Titan legend!

No Java or DotNet required. Green Energy Software! Saving the planet one bit at a time.</Char_Desc_2000></English></Program_Descriptions><Web_Info><Application_URLs><Application_Info_URL>https://netsurfer.ssuiteoffice.com/</Application_Info_URL><Application_Order_URL>https://www.ssuiteoffice.com/categories/esotericandspecialist.htm</Application_Order_URL><Application_Screenshot_URL>https://netsurfer.ssuiteoffice.com/ScreenShotMainScreen1.jpg</Application_Screenshot_URL><Application_Icon_URL>https://netsurfer.ssuiteoffice.com/NetSurfer.png</Application_Icon_URL><Application_XML_File_URL>https://www.ssuitesoft.com/PadFiles/SSuiteNetSurferPrometheus.xml</Application_XML_File_URL></Application_URLs><Download_URLs><Primary_Download_URL>https://netsurfer.ssuiteoffice.com/downloads/SetupSSuiteNetSurferPrometheus32.exe</Primary_Download_URL><Secondary_Download_URL>https://netsurfer.ssuiteoffice.com/downloads/SetupSSuiteNetSurferPrometheus64.exe</Secondary_Download_URL><Additional_Download_URL_1>https://netsurfer.ssuiteoffice.com/downloads/SSuiteNetSurferPrometheusPortable64.zip</Additional_Download_URL_1><Additional_Download_URL_2>https://netsurfer.ssuiteoffice.com/downloads/SSuiteNetSurferPrometheusPortable32.zip</Additional_Download_URL_2></Download_URLs></Web_Info><Permissions><Distribution_Permissions>Distribute this application freely at will. Let everybody know about this brilliant application.

Come visit us here:

https://www.ssuitesoft.com
https://www.ssuiteoffice.com
https://netsurfer.ssuiteoffice.com

Be Nice and Make a donation and become our HERO!

https://www.ssuiteoffice.com/donate.htm

Enjoy All our freeware software. No Java or DotNet required, Green Energy Software!</Distribution_Permissions><EULA>This software is licensed as proprietary FREEWARE. (Property of Van Loo Software(TM))

Come visit us here:

https://www.ssuitesoft.com
https://www.ssuiteoffice.com
https://netsurfer.ssuiteoffice.com

Be Nice and Make a donation and become our HERO!

https://www.ssuiteoffice.com/donate.htm

Enjoy all our free software downloads. No Java or DotNet required, Green Energy Software!</EULA></Permissions></XML_DIZ_INFO>